Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Loretta Simon, 1979-1997; 4; 13.27 cubic ft.
  - Subject Files, 1983-1997; 4.2; 1.47 cubic ft.
    - Electromagnetic Fields, 1987; 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Environment and Jobs, 1983; 1992 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Environmental Advocates, Board, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Campaign Contributions, New York State Senate Repbulicans, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Campaign Contributions, New York State Senate Repbulicans, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Campaign Contributions, New York State Senate Repbulicans, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Legislation, General, 1987-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - New York State Bar Association, Environmental Law Section, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - New York State Bar Association, Environmental Law Section, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - New York State Bar Association, Environmental Law Section, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - New York State Bar Association, Environmental Law Section, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
  - Projects, 1979-1997; 4.3; 11.0 cubic ft.
    The Projects subseries includes material related to various projects Loretta Simon championed while serving as project director for Environmental Advocates, such as billboards, pesticides, urban development, and transportation. The majority of material in this subseries relates to transportation. The inclusive dates are 1979 to 1997 with bulk dates of 1994-1996.
    - Billboards, Company Proposal, Undated (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Billboards, Guides to Outdoor Advertising, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Billboards, Highway User Fees on Outdoor Advertising, Report, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Billboards, Industry Campaign Contributions, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Billboards, Industry Campaign Contributions, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Billboards, Information, Other States, 1990; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Billboards, Legislation and Notes, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Billboards, Legislation and Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Billboards, Meetings, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Billboards, Miscellaneous, 1984-1989 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Billboards, Miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Billboards, Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Billboards, National and State Laws, Annotated, 1981-1984; 1991-1994 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Billboards, New York State Billboard Legislation, 1983-1987; 1990-1991; 1994-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Billboards, News Clippings, 1979; 1981-1984; 1988-1993 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Billboards, News Clippings, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Billboards, Opposition and Support Memorandums, 1985; 1988; 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Billboards, Route 17 Billboard Data, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Billboards, Scenic America, 1990-1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Billboards, Scenic America, Research on Billboards, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Billboards, Sign Survey, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Billboards, Syracuse City Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Billboards, Tree Cutting, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Billboards, Tree Cutting, Astoria, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Billboards, User Fees, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Billboards, Vegetation Bill, Memorandum and Bill Drafts, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Billboards, Visual Pollution and Sign Control: A Legal Handbook on Billboard Reform, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Citizen's Suit, Bills and Memorandums, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Citizen's Suit, General Information, 1991; 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Clean Air, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Clean Air, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Clean Air, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Clean Air, Bills, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Clean Air, Department of Transportation, Wetlands, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Clean Air, Dirty Donut Bill, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Clean Air, ECO Repeal, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Clean Air, "Emissions Standards for Motor Vehicles", 1992 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Clean Air, Employee Trip Reduction, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Clean Air, Employee Trip Reduction, Wisconsin, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Clean Air, General Information, 1989-1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Clean Air, Health, 1990-1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Clean Air, Low Emission Vehicles, 1991; 1992-1994 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Clean Air, Miscellaneous, 1990; 1992-1993; 1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Clean Air, MMT Gasoline Additive, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Clean Air, New Jersey, ECO, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Clean Air, Planning, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Clean Air, Questionnaire and Answers, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Clean Air, Regulations, 1991; 1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Clean Air, Toxics, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Land Use, Allegany, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Land Use, Law Center, Pace University, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Land Use, Local Institute of Land Policy, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Land Use, March 1996 Round Table, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Land Use, Parks, S6372a, Maziarz/Hoyt, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Land Use, Reports, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Land Use, Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Land Use, Transportation Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 30)
    - Lead, 1993; 1996 (Box 2 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 31)
    - Lead, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Lead, Bill 51262, 1992; 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Lead, Flyer and Script, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Lead, Information, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Lead, Press, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Lead, Special Sessions, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Lead, Worker Certification and Training, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Bills, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Citizens Advisory Council Legislation, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, Construction and Demolition Debris Disposal Legislation, 1989; 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, Great Lakes Initiative, Rochester, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, Green Plans, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, Legislative Visits, 1987-1997 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, New York State Legislation, Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, Women's Environment and Development Organization, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, Women's Health Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Pesticides, Campaign for Sustainable Agriculture, Undated (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Pesticides, DEET Decision, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Pesticides, Great Waters Report, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Pesticides, Healthy Schools Network, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Pesticides, Lawn Care and Golf Courses, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Pesticides, Legislation, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Pesticides, Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Pesticides, Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Pesticides, News Clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Pesticides, Organic Farming, 1992; 1994 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Pesticides, Reporting Bill, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Alternative Fuels, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Articles and Vendor Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Transportation, Auto Industry Credibility, Undated (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 30)
    - Transportation, Bicycle and Pedestrian Paths, Bills, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 31)
    - Transportation, Bicycle Plan Model, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 32)
    - Transportation, Bicycle Transportation, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 33)
    - Transportation, Bills, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 34)
    - Transportation, Biographies of Louis Tomson, Richard Swist, and Gene Russianoff, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 35)
    - Transportation, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 36)
    - Transportation, California Transportation Efficiency Act, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 37)
    - Transportation, Capital District Transportation Committee, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 38)
    - Transportation, Capital District Transportation Committee, Reports, 1995 April-1995 July (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 39)
    - Transportation, Capital District Fixed Guideway Transit Feasibility Study, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 40)
    - Transportation, Capital District Fixed Guideway Transit Feasibility Study, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 41)
    - Transportation, Capital District Transportation Committee, Reports, 1995 August-1995 October (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Capital District Transportation Committee, Reports, 1996 February-1996 July (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Capital District Transportation Committee, Comments and Responses to Reports, 1997 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, City Portion of Funding, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Clinton Cuts, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Coalition, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Coalition, Anne Haro, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Control Measures, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Cornell Cycles, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, D'Amato, Senator Alphonse, and Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Department of Transportation, General, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Department of Transportation, Hearings, Budget, 1996 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Department of Transportation, Wetlands, Collman, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Diesel, Bus Campaign, 1979; 1993-1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Diesel, Bus Campaign, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Diversion of Highway Funding, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Dump Diesel, Report to Levy, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Dump Diesel, 1994; 1996 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Dump Diesel, (October 1995), 1994-1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Dump Diesel, Compressed Natural Gas Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Electric Cars, Low Emission Vehicles/Zero Emissions Vehicles, 1993-1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Endorsements, Upstate Transit Coalition, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Energy, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Enhancement Surveys, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Environmental Racism, Briefing Materials, 1987; 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Executive Orders, Numbers 10-13, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Freight, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Genesee Transportation Council, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Herkimer-Oneida, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Transportation, High Speed Trains, 1992; 1994 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 30)
    - Transportation, Individuals, 1993-1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 31)
    - New Visions for Capital District Transportation, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 32)
    - New Visions for Capital District Transportation, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 33)
    - Transportation, Information, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Intelligent Vehicle-Highway System, Undated (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Appointments, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Enhancements, 1991-1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Enhancements, California, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Enhancements, Washington State, Undated (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Federal Interim Regulations and Federal Transit Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Information for Loretta Simon, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act, Report Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Land, Taking Law, 1996 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Land Use and Transportation, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Legal Changes, New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Levy Road and Bridge Bill, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Lists [names, affiliations, and contact information], Undated (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Lobby Day, 1995 March 07 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Lobbying, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Long Island, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Long Island Expressway, 1996 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Magnetically Levitated (Maglev), New York State, 1990-1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Major Investment Studies (MIS), 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Marsh Bus Company, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Mayor Rudolph Giuliani, Cuts, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Meetings and Memorandums, In-house, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Albany Questionnaire, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Conference, Buffalo, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Correspondence with Directors, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Federal, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Mailers, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Mailing List, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 30)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Maps, ca. 1992 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 31)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Members, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 32)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Pie Charts and Tables, Final Report, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 33)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Press, 1992-1995 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 34)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Public Participation, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 35)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Questionnaire, Other States Listing Information and Directories, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 36)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Report Cards, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 37)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Reports, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 38)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, State [New York], 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 39)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Statewide, 1992-1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 40)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Surveys, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 41)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Planning Organization, Surveys, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 42)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1997 (Box 5 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 43)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Transit Authority, Alternative Buses, Electric/Hybrid, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1995 Fall (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Metropolitan Transit Authority, Hearing, New York City, 1996 February (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Miscellaneous Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Montreal Protocol, Ozone, 1987 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Natural Gas Bus, 1993-1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, New York Automobile Association, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, New York City Bar Association, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, History and Organization, 1992; 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, New York State Bar Association Committee on Transportation, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, New York State Energy Office, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, New York State Public Transit Association, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 15)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, 1994-1995 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 16)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, Amendment Drafts, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 17)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, Bills, 1994-1995 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 18)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 19)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, News Coverage, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 20)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, Planning Fall, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 21)
    - Transportation, New York State Transportation Efficiency Act, Preparatory and Drafts, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 22)
    - Transportation, News Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Niagara Frontier Transportation Committee 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 24)
    - Transportation, Niagara Frontier Transportation Committee, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 25)
    - Transportation, Niagara Frontier Transportation Committee, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 26)
    - Transportation, Niagara Frontier Transportation Association and Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 27)
    - Transportation, One Person, One Vote Cases, 1973-1990 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Ozone Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 29)
    - Transportation, Pataki, George, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 30)
    - Transportation, Penn Station Redevelopment, Undated (Box 6 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 31)
    - Transportation, Philadelphia Conference, Intermodel Surface Transportation Efficiency Act of 1991, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Press Conference, 1996 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Public Participation, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Queens Meeting, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Railroads, 1994 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Regional Plan Association, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Regional Plan Association, 1996 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1991 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1991 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Reports, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Loretta Simon), Folder 11)